dropshipdirect.com 2002-12-05

# Dropship Direct : Privacy Policy

| 

**  
Your credit card and personal information is safe with DropShipDirect.com - we guarantee it!  
DropShipDirect.com respects and protects your privacy. We have designed DropShipDirect.com so that no personal identifying information is displayed online or is accessible to the general public via our web site or e-mail. _Guarantee_  
**Your browser and DropShipDirect.com's secure server encrypt confidential information during transmission, ensuring that transactions stay private and protected. DropShipDirect.com guarantees the safety of your credit card information in the following manner: if any unauthorized use of your credit card occurs as a result of your credit card purchase from DropShipDirect.com, simply notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. If, through no fault of your own, your credit card company finds credit card fraud but does not waive your entire liability for unauthorized charges, DropShipDirect.com will reimburse you for the remaining liability, up to a maximum of fifty dollars U.S. ($50.00) per card. This guarantee applies to purchases made using DropShipDirect.com's secure server (https: protocol). **_Secure Browser_**  
Your browser and DropShipDirect.com's secure server encrypt confidential information during transmission, ensuring that all superstore and clearance transactions stay private and protected When participating on our Auction site you will be given the option place online transactions over a secure server. On a secure server, your credit card information is encrypted during its transmission, ensuring that your data remains confidential. We recommend all transactions be placed via a secure server, as we are not responsible for any information placed over an unsecured server. **_Credit Card Security_**  
DropShipDirect.com reserves the right to monitor order activity to ensure a fair process. DropShipDirect.com also reserves the right to reject any order deemed to be made in bad faith, or that may be in violation of local laws, taxes or restrictions. 

We strongly advise not to test the web site with false orders, as it will result in substantial, personal legal risk. It is a violation of the law to make bids or orders under a false name or with an invalid credit card. 

DropShipDirect.com has a sophisticated Fraud Control system that screens for orders, which are subject to investigation and possible cancellation. 

For your protection, credit card orders may be delayed while screening takes place. 

Persons who commit fraudulent activity will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law. Web browsers transmit a unique address that can be used by law enforcement officials to identify fraudulent activity. Both the FBI and the US Secret Service are responsible for investigating Internet fraud cases. 

Fraudulent information will be provided to the issuing bank, shipping carriers, and networked with our business partners. 

**_Cookies_**  
DropShipDirect.com uses software tags called "cookies" to identify customers when they visit our site. They help us understand your buying preferences and customize our service to your needs. By understanding which areas of the site you visit, cookies allow us to present information, products and specials that are of personal interest to you. Our goal is to save you time and make your shopping experience unique. The information we collect with cookies is not sold, rented or shared with any outside parties. **_Use of Your Personal Information_**  
We do not sell or rent our customer information to any outside party under any circumstances. We do not reveal your e-mail address or other personal information, except to complete transactions with our third-party vendors. In such cases, we provide only the information required to complete the transaction. By contract, the third party is not permitted to sell, rent or share this information. 

During the DropShipDirect.com registration process, we ask you to provide us with contact information, such as name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, telephone number and a valid credit card number. We use this information to verify your account when you place an order. 

If you provide us with your e-mail address, register as a customer, or make a purchase from us, we will occasionally send you e-mail or standard mail with recommendations or notices of new products and prices. 

Separately, we send e-mails to keep you informed of your order status. 

Your visitor and user information is collected for the purpose of reporting to advertisers. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you, such as your name, customer number, password, e-mail address, credit card number, or transaction history. 

**_Solicited Information: Contests, Surveys, Services_**  
You may occasionally see contests, surveys, and other features of our web site that ask you to provide us with information. When you choose to respond to these requests, the information you offer may be used for several reasons, including the uses set out in the sections above. We will also provide information to third parties as necessary to meet prize fulfillment or other aspects of any contest or similar offering. If we intend to use your personal information for any other purpose, we will notify you and give you a chance to opt out before responding to our survey, contest form, or other request. Additionally, you may choose not to respond or participate in any survey, contest, or other request. **  
**

|
